(Raj:)I'm telling you, dude...
(Raj:)...the only way to feel better
about Penny going out with other guys...
(Raj:)...is for you to get back on the whores.
(Howard:)-Horse.
-What?
The phrase is "get back on the horse."
Not whores.
(Raj:)That's disgusting, dude.
No, it's not.... Never mind.
(Howard:)He is right, though.
(Howard:)If you want, I can turn you on
to this great new dating site I found.
(Leonard:)No, thanks.
(Howard:)You sure? They say
they can find a match for anybody.
(Leonard:)-Have they found a match for you?
-Tons.
(Howard:)I've had, like, eight dates
in the last month.
(Howard:)Twelve, if you count the ones
who showed up and left.
(Sheldon:)-I can't bring the nitrogen tank down.
-Why not?
(Sheldon:)All right, let me restate that.
It's very heavy and I don't want to.
(Leonard:)-I'll help you.
-Thank you.
(Sheldon:)Lift with your knees, not your back.
(Sheldon:)Good night.